stocktrak.com 2018-07-30

# Privacy Policy - StockTrak Product Pages

This website is owned and operated by Stock-Trak. Stock-Trak recognizes and respects the privacy expectations of participants in its simulations. This Privacy Statement explains how we collect, use and protect your personally identifying information (“Personal Information”) and under what circumstances it may be disclosed. This Privacy Statement is incorporated into our Agreement. All capitalized terms not defined herein are defined in that Agreement. We reserve the right to change this Privacy Statement from time to time, consistent with applicable privacy and other laws. Unless prohibited by applicable law, any such change will apply thirty (30) days from date of posting on our site, unless you object (“opt-out”) as provided below before that date. Your continued use of this site following such changes signifies your acceptance of those changes.The Information We Collect and How We Collect It

Stock-Trak collects Personal Information from registered participants. As a condition of registration, participants provide their name, address, email address and date of birth. Stock-Trak may also collect additional information from participants and other visitors to the site through cookies or web beacons as detailed below.

Stock-Trak is the sole owner of the information collected through our site. We sell, share or rent this information to others only in ways that are disclosed in this privacy statement or with your express consent.

##### Purpose of the Information

Stock-Trak collects Personal Information from our participants to facilitate our simulations’ plays, including determining participants’ eligibility. Personal Information allows us to keep track of our individual participants’ performance, advise winners of their prizes and how those prizes may be collected and publicize results. The information further allows us to contact participants to announce simulation updates, new simulations or any other information about Stock-Trak that may be of interest to a participant.

##### To Whom We Disclose the Information

Stock-Trak will only sell or disclose your Personal Information to third parties in select circumstances as detailed in the following paragraph of this Privacy Statement. First, as noted in the Agreement, we may publicize the names, likenesses and other information concerning winners of the simulations as we deem appropriate.

Second, we may disclose your Personal Information to contractors or service providers who may provide services or perform functions on our behalf, such as an information technology service provider. Those contractors and service providers are permitted to use your Personal Information only for the purpose for which it has been provided and may not disclose it to any other third party except at our express direction and consistently with this Privacy Statement.

Third, we may also disclose your Personal Information to our advertisers but only in an aggregated form that identifies participants’ demographics. When we present the information in an aggregated form, those advertisers will be not be able to identify or contact you. However, if you click on an advertisement that appears on our site, you will be taken to a third-party website, whose privacy practices will govern any information so disclosed.

Finally, we may share your Personal Information, as permitted by law, to both our affiliates and other non-affiliated third parties that offer products or services that we or they believe may be of interest to you.

##### Other Information Collected Through The Site

Stock-Trak also collects other information through its site for personalization purposes to make it more interesting for you. Our site uses cookies, which are pieces of information that a website sends to your computer while you are viewing our site. While a cookie assigns a random, unique number to your computer, it does not contain information that would personally identify you even though we can associate the cookie with any personally identifying information that you provide us while visiting our site. This cookie is exclusive to Stock-Trak and we do not provide access to the cookie to any third party. While most browsers allow you to refuse cookies, this act will limit system performance and may even cause certain site features to malfunction or not to work. For more information, please consult your browser’s “help” button.

Our site also uses “web beacons”. Web beacons are small pieces of data that are embedded in images on website pages. Web beacons allow us to analyze our site’s traffic patterns, such as the frequency with which our users visit various parts of the site. The beacons’ use may involve the transmission of information either directly to us or to another party authorized by us to collect information on our behalf. Web beacons may also be in HTML emails we send our participants and used to determine whether the participants have opened those emails or clicked on their links. Web beacons’ information may be collected in a form that is personally identifiable. If you’re a registered member of www.stocktrak.com, we use your email address to send you free email newsletters containing selected stories, market information, advertisements and links to our sites.

##### Opting Out of Changes To This Privacy Statement

From time to time, we may amend this Privacy Statement. Should any amendments create additional ways in which we may collect or disclose your Personal Information, you may opt out of those amendments by e-mailing us within 30 days of the posting of the revised Privacy Statement on the site. We will always identify the date this Privacy Statement was last revised at the top of the statement. It is your responsibility to monitor the statement periodically to determine whether there have been changes. Opting out of an amendment to this Privacy Statement may subject you to termination of your registration and participation in any ongoing or future simulations at our sole election and upon notice to you.

##### Interest-Based Advertising

We use Google or other third party partners to display interest-based advertising to you within our sites. Interest-based ads, sometimes also referred to as targeted or personalized ads, are advertisements about goods and services, that may be more useful and relevant to you, based on information gathered about your activities across non-affiliated websites. 

In order to provide interest-based ads, we use cookies, web beacons, and other similar technologies, and we may permit our third party partners to do the same. 

In providing interest-based ads, we follow the Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising developed by the Digital Advertising Alliance (DAA). To learn more, please visit [http://www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/)

You can choose not to receive interest-based ads from third parties who are members of the Network Advertising Initiative (NAI) or who follow the DAA’s Self-Regulatory Principles for Online Behavioral Advertising by visiting the opt-out pages on the NAI website <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/> and DAA website <http://www.aboutads.info/choices/>

Note that if you “opt-out” you will still see online ads, but they will not be personalized.

##### Corrections

To correct Personal Information you have submitted or if you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, contact: Customer Service at help-desk{at}stocktrak.com

Last revised on November 21st, 2017.
